How much longer to the embassy?
I believe it'll be around twenty minutes, sir.
Huh?
The brakes aren't working.
Hey! In front of you! Watch out! Stop!
One of our diplomats lost their life
in a car accident while visitng Ostania.
We suspect this was an assassination
by the East's Republican Party.
It's becoming clearer by day that they're
trying to force Westalis into an all-out war.
We must uncover their plot,
no matter the cost.
Let's put him on the job.
With stakes this high,
we need the best agent we got,
Twilight.
Here are the goods, as promised.
This proves the foreign minister wears a toupee.
I even have the negatives.
Well done.
This will help seal his resignation.
Pleasure doing business.
Hey.
How about you hand over those goods now?
Huh? Wha—But you were just—
I got duped!
Code name: Twilight.
Occupation: spy.
In an era where the nations of the world
fight a fierce information war in the shadows,
this man has survived by being a master of disguise,
capable of donning hundreds of different faces.
Daddy's been in such a foul mood lately
'cause someone stole pics of his toupee or something.
What even? Ugh, I'm so mad.
Are you even listening, Robert?
Hmm? Ah, yes. That's a shame.
So, Robert, do you think that'll be us one day?
Karen, let's break up.
What?!
A rock would make for a more
engaging conversational partner.
Best of luck in your future endeavours.
Hey, Robert! Hey!
You can't just walk out on me!
Robert!
Sorry, Karen, but I have
no further use for you or your family.
As of tonight, I'm done
donning the mask of Robert.
Marriage? Conventional happiness?
I buried those aspirations with my identity
the day I became a spy.
Meow.
Must be Cipher C.
The train bound for Berlint
is now departing from track five.
Good day. Or perhaps, good evening, Twilight.
Excellent work on your last assignment.
Thanks to you, the minister lives another day,
to the great benefit of our country.
Now, without further ado,
here is your next mission.
Your target is the head of
the National Unity Party, Donovan Desmond.
He poses a grave threat to the truce
between the East and the West.
Your mission is to get close to him
and probe for any seditious activities.
In order to achieve this goal,
you are to get married and bear a child.
Say what?
Desmond is an extremely cautious man
who rarely shows his face in public.
He only makes public appearances at social gatherings
held at the elite private school his son attends.
They serve as informal get-togethers for
the upper echelon of industrial and political leaders.
Your child will enrol in this school
and infiltrate one of these gatherings.
The enrolment deadline is drawing near.
You only have one week to pull this off.
You expect me to produce a child
within seven days?!
Excuse me.
We call it Operation Strix.
It's the key to maintaining peace between
the East and West—perhaps even the world at large.
Hero who casts no shadow,
the great deeds of you and your fellow agents
shall never see the light of day.
You will never be awarded a medal,
let alone receive public fanfare.
But don't forget,
the peaceful lives of our citizens
are a product of your blood, sweat, and tears.
Fine.